# Priyank Garg

Gurgaon, India | Linkedin | +91-9755443790 | priyankgarg28@gmail.com

### **EXECUTIVE SUMMARY**

Product Manager with 6+ years of experience in launching, managing and building B2C and B2B technology products across Customer Service, Identity Verification, AI decisioning, Data Platform, Buy Now Pay Later (BNPL) and Partner & Sales enablement; helped 1000x transaction volume growth over 3 years; achieve 30% more transaction volumes through AI assisted underwriting

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

IndusInd Bank Gurgaon, India

DVP Product - Consumer Banking

Aug 2024 - Present

- Onboarding new dialer to increase coverage and contacability rate by 30%
- Implementing new changes in CRM to drive ANR growth by 10%

# Creditvidya (acquired by CRED)

Hyderabad, India

Jan 2021 - Aug 2024

Product Manager, Customer Experience and Platform

- Defined customer service product strategy with roadmap for next 4 quarters in place.
  Collaborated with cross-functional teams to build a configurable and embeddable helpdesk widget, leading to a 15% increase
- in %tickets/prospect.
  Conducted A/B test over two versions of widget to finalise design which had 25% higher clicks/prospect.
- Led user feedback loop process to continuously improve the widget's functionality, leading to a 7% increase in CSAT within give months.
- Introduced IVRs in two languages Hindi and English with a deflection ratio of 33%.
- Retained users who were on last EMIs or repaid the loan through **Top-up and Closed loan product** bringing **20%** of monthly transaction volume.
- Personalised the experience for bounced users by building Retargeting product and grow monthly transaction volumes by 10%.
- Increased credit score generation per user by 7% by improving experience, bug fixing and building fallback mechanisms in backend
- Accelerated the KYC completion rate by 15% through a new identity verification experience.
- Invented a new AI enabled smart upload feature which enabled additional 10% users to upload files.
- Orchestrated the customer experience and partner enablement for the Buy Now Pay Later (BNPL) product leading to \$5 Mn worth of monthly transaction volumes.
- Conceived a partner enablement platform as a SaaS MVP for tracking loan application status, reporting, & access management for partner backend and sales teams used by 15+ partners.

NeoGrowth Credit Mumbai, India

Associate Product Manager, Analytics and Platform

May 2018 - Jan 2021

- Deployed a bank statement analysis engine NeoScore which brought down the turnaround time for underwriters from 30 minutes earlier to 5 minutes by automating the process to evaluate users financial fitness.
- Interviewed 150+ merchants from 5 different cities, created personas, identified problems & presented insights to leadership team.
- Collaborated with PMs to build a new product "NeoExpress" for lower ticket size loans occupying **50%** of monthly transaction volume in next 3 months.
- Executed product improvements for "Alliance portal" (B2B web application) for **20+ partners** and "NG Sales app" (Android) for **200+** on-field agents such as Bulk upload, digital application form for sales app, onboarding journey.

## **EDUCATION**

**Institute of Management Technology** 

Ghaziabad, India

MBA, Finance

Graduation Date: Mar 2018

Graduation Date: Dec 2014

Birla Institute of Technology and Science, Pilani

Goa, India

Bachelor of Engineering, Electronics and Instrumentation

**SKILLS** 

SQL | JIRA | Posthog | Amplitude | Excel | Figma | Notion | Whimsical | Confluence